export const ALL_ANSWERS=['go ( hang out đi chơi )', 'do', 'work', 'learn/ study', 'answer', 'ask ( câu hỏi question)', 'play ( trò chơi game)', 'need', 'want/would like', 'take', 'give', 'like', 'come to', 'visit', 'see', 'look ( tôi nhìn thấy) i see', 'understand', 'open', 'close', 'know', 'find', 'love', '(bỏ) leave', 'think', 'to rest / break time', 'buy', 'sell', 'eat', 'drink', 'take', 'help', 'have', 'miss', 'remember to', 'waiting for', 'move', 'help', 'stand up', 'sit down', 'lay down', 'sleep', 'stupid (adjective)', 'meet', 'run', 'walk', 'hear', 'read', 'speak / say', 'write', 'send', 'stop', 'turn on', 'turn off', 'receive', 'decide', 'marry', 'divorce', 'angry', 'to plan', 'laugh', 'cry', 'smile', 'to finish/end', 'start/begin', 'live', 'die', 'draw', 'sing', 'dance', 'shower', 'pee (acceptable only for babies)', 'poop ( cứt shit - noun)', 'busy', 'prepare', 'repeat', 'remind', 'cancel', 'booking', 'call', 'return', 'brush teeth', 'hit/ fight', 'to punch', 'wash', 'wash hair', 'wash clothes', 'watch', 'use', 'slap', 'touch', 'wake up', 'to joke', 'take hand', 'feel', 'propose', 'kiss', 'hug', 'come back', 'to go away (cút đi -never come back)', 'talking/ chatting', 'texting']
export const VIET_WORDS=[{'question': '\ufeffđi', 'answer': 'go ( hang out đi chơi )', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['learn / study', 'understand', 'to plan'], 'id': 6922035156}, {'question': 'làm', 'answer': 'do', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['read', 'wash clothes', 'move'], 'id': 7842813235}, {'question': 'làm việc', 'answer': 'work', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['understand', 'turn off', 'hear'], 'id': 6488324518}, {'question': 'học', 'answer': 'learn / study', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['touch', 'touch', 'wash clothes'], 'id': 2920489179}, {'question': 'trả lời', 'answer': 'answer', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['close', 'booking', 'hug'], 'id': 6167944084}, {'question': 'hỏi', 'answer': 'ask ( câu hỏi question)', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['run', 'sell', 'to punch'], 'id': 4740347391}, {'question': 'chơi', 'answer': 'play ( trò chơi game)', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['have', 'give', 'visit'], 'id': 1609980463}, {'question': 'cần', 'answer': 'need', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['stop', 'visit', 'to finish / end'], 'id': 2569281542}, {'question': 'muốn', 'answer': 'want / would like', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['start / begin', 'call', 'run'], 'id': 2579154948}, {'question': 'lấy', 'answer': 'take', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['look ( tôi nhìn thấy) i see', 'come back', 'shower'], 'id': 1213035853}, {'question': 'cho', 'answer': 'give', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['need', 'kiss', 'propose'], 'id': 7143517035}, {'question': 'thích', 'answer': 'like', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['use', 'divorce', 'start / begin'], 'id': 7660116651}, {'question': 'đến', 'answer': 'come to', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['slap', 'to plan', 'move'], 'id': 2933438296}, {'question': 'thăm', 'answer': 'visit', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['to joke', 'kiss', 'start / begin'], 'id': 8459421546}, {'question': 'thấy', 'answer': 'see', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['do', 'to joke', 'laugh'], 'id': 7839430993}, {'question': 'nhìn', 'answer': 'look ( tôi nhìn thấy) i see', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['divorce', 'slap', 'to rest / break time'], 'id': 6586968172}, {'question': 'hiểu', 'answer': 'understand', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['hug', 'kiss', 'prepare'], 'id': 5219276581}, {'question': 'mở', 'answer': 'open', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['meet', 'watch', 'to finish / end'], 'id': 8376166747}, {'question': 'đóng', 'answer': 'close', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['take', 'to rest / break time', 'miss'], 'id': 4697267829}, {'question': 'biết', 'answer': 'know', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['shower', 'busy', 'turn off'], 'id': 8838158599}, {'question': 'tìm', 'answer': 'find', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['stand up', 'go ( hang out đi chơi )', 'cry'], 'id': 2564122546}, {'question': 'yêu', 'answer': 'love', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['sleep', 'take', 'brush teeth'], 'id': 7457605980}, {'question': 'rời khỏi', 'answer': '(bỏ) leave', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['take', 'help', 'sing'], 'id': 1535658748}, {'question': 'nghĩ', 'answer': 'think', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['meet', 'return', 'read'], 'id': 9659912052}, {'question': 'nghỉ', 'answer': 'to rest / break time', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['poop ( cứt shit - noun)', 'brush teeth', 'poop ( cứt shit - noun)'], 'id': 4238472069}, {'question': 'mua', 'answer': 'buy', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['learn / study', 'wash', 'poop ( cứt shit - noun)'], 'id': 2310417992}, {'question': 'bán', 'answer': 'sell', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['sleep', 'propose', 'do'], 'id': 7078305758}, {'question': 'ăn', 'answer': 'eat', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['to rest / break time', 'meet', 'send'], 'id': 1878481412}, {'question': 'uống', 'answer': 'drink', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['like', 'touch', 'visit'], 'id': 6865667284}, {'question': 'cầm', 'answer': 'take', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['start / begin', 'start / begin', 'hear'], 'id': 7991966545}, {'question': 'giúp', 'answer': 'help', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['to plan', 'slap', 'move'], 'id': 2937860216}, {'question': 'có', 'answer': 'have', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['turn off', 'slap', 'use'], 'id': 5201541467}, {'question': 'nhớ ( nhớ nhung)', 'answer': 'miss', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['live', 'booking', 'write'], 'id': 1979305649}, {'question': 'ghi nhớ', 'answer': 'remember to', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['sing', 'live', 'sit down'], 'id': 9406775611}, {'question': 'chờ đợi', 'answer': 'waiting for', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['drink', 'take hand', 'to punch'], 'id': 3159340765}, {'question': 'di chuyển', 'answer': 'move', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['waiting for', 'close', 'to punch'], 'id': 8808091711}, {'question': 'giúp đỡ', 'answer': 'help', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['understand', 'sing', 'sleep'], 'id': 2106274552}, {'question': 'đứng', 'answer': 'stand up', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['need', 'miss', 'waiting for'], 'id': 7300062361}, {'question': 'ngồi', 'answer': 'sit down', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['know', 'come back', 'laugh'], 'id': 3489360652}, {'question': 'nằm', 'answer': 'lay down', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['(bỏ) leave', 'return', 'poop ( cứt shit - noun)'], 'id': 9459847012}, {'question': 'ngủ', 'answer': 'sleep', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['sing', 'wake up', 'live'], 'id': 1700465073}, {'question': 'ngu', 'answer': 'stupid (adjective)', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['cancel', 'remind', 'drink'], 'id': 3187417889}, {'question': 'gặp', 'answer': 'meet', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['remember to', 'sleep', 'give'], 'id': 3539971185}, {'question': 'chạy', 'answer': 'run', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['remind', 'wash clothes', 'smile'], 'id': 1627533644}, {'question': 'đi bộ', 'answer': 'walk', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['drink', 'walk', 'to punch'], 'id': 7013297348}, {'question': 'nghe', 'answer': 'hear', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['divorce', 'have', 'draw'], 'id': 7514557419}, {'question': 'đọc', 'answer': 'read', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['slap', '(bỏ) leave', 'decide'], 'id': 5641405956}, {'question': 'nói', 'answer': 'speak / say', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['understand', 'take', 'wash hair'], 'id': 5544312148}, {'question': 'viết', 'answer': 'write', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['cry', 'to plan', 'dance'], 'id': 8821475189}, {'question': 'gửi', 'answer': 'send', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['decide', 'cancel', 'stand up'], 'id': 5022671681}, {'question': 'dừng lại', 'answer': 'stop', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['to punch', 'open', 'draw'], 'id': 3528586867}, {'question': 'bật', 'answer': 'turn on', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['laugh', 'think', 'help'], 'id': 5180483502}, {'question': 'tắt', 'answer': 'turn off', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['wash hair', 'play ( trò chơi game)', 'texting'], 'id': 6238013479}, {'question': 'nhận', 'answer': 'receive', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['have', 'stupid (adjective)', 'need'], 'id': 5140492644}, {'question': 'quyết định', 'answer': 'decide', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['go ( hang out đi chơi )', 'turn on', 'stand up'], 'id': 9788169271}, {'question': 'cưới', 'answer': 'marry', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['think', 'die', 'close'], 'id': 9847213128}, {'question': 'ly hôn', 'answer': 'divorce', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['stupid (adjective)', 'lay down', 'cry'], 'id': 5898421728}, {'question': 'tức giận', 'answer': 'angry', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['sing', 'meet', 'receive'], 'id': 9658876109}, {'question': 'lên kế hoạch', 'answer': 'to plan', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['booking', 'live', 'to go away (cút đi -never come back)'], 'id': 7659689672}, {'question': 'cười', 'answer': 'laugh', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['see', 'busy', 'help'], 'id': 8853711713}, {'question': 'khóc', 'answer': 'cry', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['move', 'die', 'come to'], 'id': 6456802014}, {'question': 'mỉm cười', 'answer': 'smile', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['sing', 'send', 'hit / fight'], 'id': 6323686250}, {'question': 'kết thúc', 'answer': 'to finish / end', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['do', 'wash hair', 'find'], 'id': 2675972177}, {'question': 'bắt đầu', 'answer': 'start / begin', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['wake up', 'smile', 'sleep'], 'id': 3566322195}, {'question': 'sống', 'answer': 'live', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['write', 'to joke', 'wash hair'], 'id': 1321286030}, {'question': 'chết', 'answer': 'die', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['die', 'understand', 'repeat'], 'id': 8789071858}, {'question': 'vẽ', 'answer': 'draw', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['speak / say', 'waiting for', 'understand'], 'id': 5073243500}, {'question': 'hát', 'answer': 'sing', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['find', 'return', 'help'], 'id': 3928886106}, {'question': 'nhảy', 'answer': 'dance', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['prepare', 'busy', 'to plan'], 'id': 8307956541}, {'question': 'tắm', 'answer': 'shower', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['eat', 'die', 'meet'], 'id': 3445167008}, {'question': 'đi đái', 'answer': 'pee (acceptable only for babies)', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['hug', 'lay down', 'pee (acceptable only for babies)'], 'id': 2360241045}, {'question': 'đi ị ( ỉa)', 'answer': 'poop ( cứt shit - noun)', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['take', 'receive', 'wash'], 'id': 5949861947}, {'question': 'bận', 'answer': 'busy', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['cancel', 'help', 'draw'], 'id': 5712072669}, {'question': 'chuẩn bị', 'answer': 'prepare', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['help', 'give', 'lay down'], 'id': 5170397547}, {'question': 'nhắc lại', 'answer': 'repeat', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['laugh', 'hug', 'have'], 'id': 6813552721}, {'question': 'nhắc nhở ( ngợi nhớ)', 'answer': 'remind', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['decide', 'to rest / break time', 'to rest / break time'], 'id': 1824453445}, {'question': 'hủy', 'answer': 'cancel', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['turn on', 'visit', 'drink'], 'id': 1559407769}, {'question': 'đặt', 'answer': 'booking', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['stand up', 'drink', 'slap'], 'id': 9188262470}, {'question': 'gọi', 'answer': 'call', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['to plan', 'texting', 'watch'], 'id': 7157237909}, {'question': 'trở lại', 'answer': 'return', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['use', 'busy', 'die'], 'id': 5667363612}, {'question': 'đánh răng', 'answer': 'brush teeth', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['die', 'speak / say', 'hug'], 'id': 3322638055}, {'question': 'đánh / đánh nhau', 'answer': 'hit / fight', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['run', 'slap', 'pee (acceptable only for babies)'], 'id': 5288514424}, {'question': 'đấm', 'answer': 'to punch', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['answer', 'give', 'meet'], 'id': 7460290792}, {'question': 'rửa', 'answer': 'wash', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['shower', 'pee (acceptable only for babies)', 'help'], 'id': 9405346548}, {'question': 'gội đầu', 'answer': 'wash hair', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['wake up', 'buy', 'do'], 'id': 1774333156}, {'question': 'giặt quần áo', 'answer': 'wash clothes', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['help', 'want / would like', 'to plan'], 'id': 4784134436}, {'question': 'xem', 'answer': 'watch', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['hit / fight', 'decide', 'miss'], 'id': 9060006292}, {'question': 'sử dụng', 'answer': 'use', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['understand', 'draw', 'love'], 'id': 2368068530}, {'question': 'tát', 'answer': 'slap', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['wash clothes', 'come to', 'draw'], 'id': 3979200537}, {'question': 'sờ', 'answer': 'touch', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['feel', 'meet', 'turn on'], 'id': 8876369730}, {'question': 'thức dậy', 'answer': 'wake up', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['busy', 'to go away (cút đi -never come back)', 'stupid (adjective)'], 'id': 4565677673}, {'question': 'đùa', 'answer': 'to joke', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['close', 'call', 'lay down'], 'id': 3240271217}, {'question': 'cầm tay', 'answer': 'take hand', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['wash', 'sit down', 'close'], 'id': 9342941648}, {'question': 'cảm thấy', 'answer': 'feel', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['buy', 'cry', 'poop ( cứt shit - noun)'], 'id': 2879796398}, {'question': 'cầu hôn', 'answer': 'propose', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['speak / say', 'laugh', 'talking / chatting'], 'id': 2131557145}, {'question': 'hôn', 'answer': 'kiss', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['laugh', 'send', 'start / begin'], 'id': 1368048878}, {'question': 'ôm', 'answer': 'hug', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['remind', 'pee (acceptable only for babies)', 'to punch'], 'id': 9165422501}, {'question': 'trở về', 'answer': 'come back', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['watch', 'help', 'visit'], 'id': 5653923137}, {'question': 'đi đi', 'answer': 'to go away (cút đi -never come back)', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['like', 'draw', 'wash hair'], 'id': 9309576639}, {'question': 'trò chuyện', 'answer': 'talking / chatting', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['marry', 'take', 'call'], 'id': 9727028625}, {'question': 'nhắn tin', 'answer': 'texting', 'category': 'Vietnamese Class Vocab 3', 'options': ['want / would like', 'sleep', 'have'], 'id': 8168099251}]

